a few weeks ago I was scrolling on
YouTube and I came across a teamu ad for
a really high-end Electronics device it
kind of looked like a Nintendo switch
for only $13 and I thought to myself who
is actually falling for this like
obviously this is a scam you're not
going to end up getting the Nintendo
switch and if you do it's just going to
be an electronic box it's going to have
nothing actually on it but then I
realized I may be wrong and I just have
some preconceived notions of Teemu and
I'm happy to be wrong and so that is why
today I'll be putting it to a test by
purchasing about a dozen different Teemu
items that were listed for very cheap to
see if they're actually legit and we're
talking some crazy products they're
touting raging from a translation pen to
an 8K drone all the way to an entire
Apple watch for pennies on the dollar so
obviously we have a lot to do so without
further Ado grab your popcorn and let's
do this so the very first teu scam ad
we're looking at I mean there is
absolutely no way this is legit it's a
$115 basically Apple watch that you can
get by a company named black view it's
an AI Voice Assistant it said that it's
compatible with Android and iPhone
answer slake calls suitable for
Halloween or Christmas perfect gift for
the family and friends 4.7 stars there
is no way I am calling cap on this I
cannot believe you can get an Apple
Watch for $15 I don't care if it's the
number one best seller from this seller
what does that even mean so it has
arrived so here it is right here
Smartwatch R50 um it says it's made in
China but the address is in Madrid I
don't understand really kind of what's
happening there but we're going to try
this out I'm going to give it a fair
shot I mean I'd love to have a $15 Apple
watch so let's see if it's actually
worth it all right the
unboxing okay I mean it's certainly a
piece of technology pretty nice band
actually on it too kind of reminds me of
like a Fitbit band and initial
impression is it doesn't really hurt it
feels pretty strong so I'm going to go
ahead and charge this and see if we can
ultimately use it oh wait a second it's
turning on oh okay I like how defaults
to English even though it's clearly
should be in Mandarin all right so
they're asking me to pair and to please
download with defit app so it's just
Chinese want my data fine you could have
it okay so I downloaded the defit app
and it looks like it's already sensing
me yeah so I'm going to pair it up and
look I'm already synced up it has the
actual time as well it recognizes that
it's 649 in US time I guess we're using
military time but now let's actually
test this out see what this baby can do
there's no way this thing can track my
sleep and heart rate for $14 all right
I'm a skeptic I'm going to actually test
out I'm going to take a couple of steps
and see if it actually works to see if
it can track
that a few moments later I don't know
how many steps I just took so my
editor's going to have the amount of
steps I just took on screen but now this
is the amount of steps that the app is
telling me that I took so I don't know
if it's close if it is close then that's
crazy even if it's not that close it is
kind of cool that it is able to track
that sleep as well heart rate okay let's
try and get my heart rate all right it's
measuring my heart rate right now 83
which feels kind of right because I'm
moving around a little bit usually I'm
resting at like 65 all right so you can
even make a phone call so I'm going to
go ahead and call myself so dial pad
calling please enter your password how
does it do that did you hear that please
enter your password then press pound
this thing is a phone too so this is a
phone it's an Apple Watch it's like a
health this is $13 that's actually crazy
that blows my mind I know that it's
using Bluetooth to use my cellular
service but the fact it has a speaker on
it and headphone Port so you could like
talk and listen from it and use it as an
Apple Watch I feel like this is as good
as it gets what else am I missing this
is honestly insane I think overall this
is probably one of the best items that
I've ever seen for that cheap WOW Teemu
okay genuinely impressed did not expect
that this next product is an absolute
juggernaut they are selling for $37 as
part of teu week free shipping and $5
credit for any delay they are selling a
game boy or a handheld console is what
they call it but it's basically it looks
like a Game Boy Color and you're able to
go through and it actually has games on
it which I don't understand how it has
that capability but here it is right
here it came in game console looks just
like the picture actually quite nice
boxing and stuff tells you a lot of
information on the back it tells you
some more compatibilities so we're going
to crack this open and I'm going to look
to play some games all right what does a
$37 gaming console look like let's see
if China is really eating our lunch okay
it's very nice and what I will say is it
has bumpers on the back it has like lnr
buttons which is really cool actually it
has like a really nice retro look I mean
it is actually a real device and what's
cool is it's USBC charged so it doesn't
like require any batteries or anything
so I'm going to turn this on let's see
if it has any
battery oh look at that it does okay
open source console is what they call it
on the screen the rs65 okay so there's
the operating system it's loading up
right now it's it's loading up all these
different games it says Sega I saw
Nintendo before this Microsoft options
now it's starting the UI wa this has so
many games on it let me show you what
this has on it this is crazy okay so
check this out I think this thing
literally has over a 100 games so I'm
going through this these are all like
Capcom system games so you'll see Street
Fighter 1 2 more Street Fighter Mega Man
scoobydoo that's crazy this thing has
everything wait so does it have Beyond
Capcom games too like can I get some
Nintendo games okay so it's just it has
32 capcon games but I'm going to
actually play one to see if it works
okay so I played a random game I got un
Squadron wow this thing is actually
legit Show's the guy with the mustache I
do like a good mustache I'm in shock I
can't believe this is real you know
devices like this make me sad because
the fact that China is able to build a
console that's honestly pretty solid for
$37 discounted sometimes probably to
like $30 and you can get a really great
device in which you have an entire
catalog of games it really makes me
upset to see that nintend nintend Sony
Microsoft they priced their consoles at
like $500 I know that China can actually
come up with a legitimate like Nintendo
switch for like 10000 bucks this is just
proof of it this is sick and it has
really good graphics I don't know if you
can actually tell but the graphics are
quite good look at the graphics of
Street Fighter this is better graphics
than probably my PC I can't click a so I
can't fight back so I just lost trust me
I'm actually pretty decent at this game
but look at this high quality Street
Fighter that's how you know a device
like this is actually worth the money if
you care about these types of games
oh you're still here okay I definitely
wasn't playing for the last like 6
minutes but overall that is a really
cool device so it looks like another dub
for Teemu and I'm going to have to give
that like a n out of 10 for how cheap as
it was and how good the quality was it
doesn't really get any better but this
next one is where I think Teemu is
actually going to start losing some
points and credibility because there is
no shot that for $60 you can get your
own mechanical pet dog because that is
what I purchased a wireless remote
control dog AI voice control be deobia
Yak Can Dance full of sci-fi that's what
I'm excited to try so let's go ahead and
open this can't believe I just bought
myself a dog like that all right here
she is smart toy dog very
straightforward I mean just by the size
of this box it must be a small dog
please don't be a scam please don't be a
scam please don't be a
scam okay so it is actually here it is
called a smart dog looks like the name
of the company is called smart dog now
look what it says it can do we're
talking greetings Kung Fu swimming sit
down attack and handstand well I'm going
to test all six of those and we're going
to see if it can do this all right meet
our dog I have like an entire Xbox
controller to control it that is a lot
of things okay so this is our dog right
here I'm going to turn him
on dog
sit
sit oh what every now and then he just
looks at me and he does something really
scary can you hear me good boy oh look
at him he's so scary yo what's up guys
just got my new dog isn't he so gorgeous
hey what's your name I forget your name
I didn't name you I guess I'm going to
call you Sam puppy cha right you're a
good boy can you sit can you show the
camera can you
sit that wasn't a sit but okay pretty
close can you do something else for the
camera come on show them your eyes don't
be afraid here how about I give you a
little push oh oh crap I'm sorry you
shouldn't have seen that all right so I
mean overall I would have to say that
this thing was a tad of a down but it
was actually a little bit scary but it
was also kind of cute so simultaneously
I think it was a dub but I just wouldn't
suggest getting
it I'd just like to emphasize again do
not get this puppy I forgot to give the
dog a rating and considering he's
probably going to like bark at me if I
don't give him a high score this is
going to be a very scared 8.2 out of 10
okay he seems happy with it are you
happy with an 8.2
[Music]
moving on moving on we've had some cool
ones so far but this one may just be the
coolest one yet so we'll see if it's
actually legit or just another teu scam
although so far they're pretty solid I
must say I'm very impressed 4.7 stars
with 1,200 reviews and for only $16 you
can get yourself a lightsaber that's
right so I went ahead and bought it and
here it is so I'm going to try it out
light sword epe leer which I think is
French for light sword that would make
sense so let's open this up I'm actually
a little afraid of this I hope that it's
not dangerous because I don't usually do
well with dangerous toys and you'll
notice it comes in 15 colors so I think
I got all 15 colors which means it
should be changing too is this thing
going to like go on fire like how does
this work okay so here it is very heavy
piece of metal as like the grip part of
it and then guess all I do is fire this
up take off the plastic and turn it
on
wa you see
this oh what's his name uh dark Darth
Maul I'm Darth
Maul I'm
Yoda I'm uh Princess Lea Leila Leila
Leia I'm oh no my Star Wars references
are exhausted now I'm Obi-Wan
Kenobi oh uh I'm Anakin
Skywalker I I think I did Pink already
okay I think I can stop the charade so I
only have seven colors it looks like
it's not actually hot all it is is just
like a light stick now what would happen
this is a good theoretical what would
happen if a samurai fought a Jedi master
so I've become a bit of a swordsmith
over the last couple of months uh and it
looks like my Katana is much bigger than
the lightsaber and I believe I don't
know the exact like pokemony behind like
what is super critical to the other but
I think that metal would beat plasma
that sounds right like this thing would
easily take down who's the V villain
Darth Vader kind of fun though like if I
was a little kid and I was playing
against somebody and I just wanted to
like do some play Star Wars fights it'd
be a good gift to somebody so for $16 I
could see why it's the second
bestselling item have been Electronics
honestly I recommend I'd say I give this
a solid 7.4 out of 10 not bad all right
so this next item I bought is actually
the number one best-selling electric
massage thing on teu and for $15 you get
this insanely it looks like your F on
fire but like this insanely
technologically advanced foot massager
so I'm excited to try this out because
there's no way for $14 I'm going to be
able to get a foot massage let's try it
out it has really good reviews as well
lots of five stars 4.7 on 5,000 reviews
let's see if it's legit all right so
here we have it she arrived uh it just
says foot massager it's made by a
company called renai so kind of official
I guess interestingly it just opens up
so it might have been used and you never
want to have a used foot massager I
don't like how easily that opened but
here it is it looks exactly like the
picture so I'm not catfished I'll open
this up more yeah I mean that's
basically it right same thing pretty
much so I'm going to plug this bad boy
in turn it on and I'm going to get
myself a foot massage right now try not
to show too much feet all right so there
we have it it is plugged in and
everything so I'm going to see if this
turns on oh it does wow look at that and
it is the same orange as it shows on the
website got a lot of different modes
here I guess that's like the reverse
okay yeah we're going clockwise now this
is to speed it up and that's to slow it
down all right so now I'm going to try
it on my feet so going to take off my
socks don't look all right let's do
this honestly pleasantly surprised with
how this felt I think overall this is
one of the better foot massages I've had
and for that cheap $15 I mean I hate to
say it but teu takes care of your feet
so $15 I mean given all the value i'
have to give this like an8 and2 out of
10 so honestly recommend moving on this
next teamu product we're testing is a
wearable mini body cam so it shoots in
1080P and apparently it's just like a
GoPro but it's only $16 and it's the
28th bestselling item in surveillance
camera so it's not very popular but it
does have really good reviews and I
thought this was interesting cuz for $16
to have like meta Ray band quality on
your chest is pretty awesome so here we
have it right here I mean as you can see
it's pretty small it's about like the
same height as your heart would be
something like that look at it compared
to the mic it's not very big okay now I
don't know how this works oh cool so
there's a bunch of little buttons on
here and it basically allows you to I
think take a picture record uh and it's
1080P and it's fish lens so I'm excited
to see what the quality looks like let
me just charge it up and then I will
walk around oh it's already charged so
here it is okay I have to put an SD card
and everything so let me go ahead and
configure this and then I will go upload
the footage and I will show you what it
looks like okay for reference this is
what it's going to look like so it's
pretty obvious that I'm wearing it so
you can't really like finesse but let's
go ahead and just like walk around the
room and you'll see my POV of what it's
looking at all right we're going around
the room so there's a light okay a few
moments later all right well that's
embarrassing because I actually just
walked around basically the entirety of
my upstairs I'm sure you can see some
footage through like this webcam um and
it ended up having like a corrupt SD
file because it was incompatible with
this device which means this device
can't even store a recording on it
unless my SD card is just like
incompatible but that wouldn't make
sense because it's the same SD card that
I use for my camera and for my video
camera so therefore I think this device
is just actually trash so I'm actually
happy we finally got an actual scam
Teemu product this just does not work
and if it does work then I'm sorry but
you have to have it compatible with
standard SD cards I don't know what's
happening so of course this is going to
be like a zero out of 10 it just doesn't
work it doesn't do anything it said it
was recording but then you can't even
access the recording so if a tree falls
in a far does it even make a sound so
this is trash this next teamu product
was way too good to be true it's the
number 12 rated in local warehouse
stores for lighting and ceiling fans and
it is this insane holographic projection
light so of course it's not going to
create this I'm going to definitely like
taper expectations but look at that
jellyfish I mean it looks sick if it can
do like 1% of this I'd say that it's
pretty sick so it's got a 4.9 star out
of 37 reviews everyone's saying it's
amazing nice works well not as the
pictures but it is impressive which is
honestly a very fair review so for $42
if I can get like this massive
holographic stuff get like you know a
samucha holograph could just be like
chilling in the background I'd say
that's a win so let's test this out all
right so it is a lot smaller than
expected but you know what maybe it
packs a a punch so I don't want to judge
it yet now it runs on Wi-Fi phone HD
just has like a bunch of buzzwords on it
I don't care about your buzzwords I care
about your holography so let's see if it
actually does anything okay kind of
looks difficult to set up let me show
you what they gave me like what is this
okay so it's like a fan so I think
that's how it ultimately is put together
and so if I plug this in and if I
basically blast it with like some
imagery it's going to show the image
which could be a lot of fun so let's do
this
oh oh what
the it broke the dream is dead we have
to check the footage I don't know if you
saw what it was doing I didn't have time
to process it so I didn't see if like an
image was coming we're going to have to
check the instant replay on that one but
I don't know if it's a scam or not I
don't know if it works it literally
broke that is sad to see you hate to see
that now I don't know how this is
possible but there's a translation pen
which like you can highlight text and it
could translate it in real time it's
only $25 and it's basically like chat
GPT in like language form so you can
just like highlight something and it
tells you about it so here we have it it
is the intelligent scanning translation
dictionary which is I thought it was
going to be like a fun acronym but it's
not uh so this is the pen so let's open
it up and let's try this out okay so I
mean as expected it's pretty small it's
just a pen it kind of looks like a taser
want to tase somebody okay so here we
have it Chinese to English let's do the
opposite I want to do English to Chinese
so I'm just supposed to like scan this
across and see if it works okay so here
it is English to Chinese Precision
scanning whoa are you kidding me how did
it do that wait that's crazy this
actually worked all right let me try
something else okay I'm going to try
game
console go no no
no n SOS all right let's try one word at
a time P okay I don't think I can read
this console this is actually quite an
amazing tool how just in real time it's
just able to scan and then tell you how
to say something in Chinese or you could
do any language really so it has a bunch
I mean I'm really impressed so I'm going
to give that like a 9.3 out of 10 this
next item might just be the coolest item
on teu if it actually exists I'm very
skeptical but for $37 you can get an 8K
drone and look it has like these beads
that you could shoot out of it so it's
like a carbon fiber Weaponry 8K drone
for $37 and you'll see it comes with all
these different things I went ahead and
bought it so here it is it is called the
k11 shoot brushless continuous uh and
it's showing it's a drone that shoots
little Pebbles that is crazy Crystal
bullets they call it now I'll probably
do this outside but part me just wants
to open this right now so maybe I'll
just do that I feel like I have the cops
called on me if they see this device
outside everyone was wondering where the
drones in New Jersey were coming from
they're coming from my house I guess all
right moment of truth
uh okay the beads are very tiny I mean
those are really tiny the Drone is also
quite small I don't believe this is
going to be 8K let me reserve my
judgment until I try it okay I'm going
to go outside and I'm going to record
this all right so I just finished
putting in the AAA battery so the remote
is now ready to go so I'm going to turn
this puppy on and see if we'll take
flight okay here we
go I am pressing every V oh here we go
it wasn't on sorry about that that here
we go now take
flight what was
that this thing is junk this thing is
literally not even working how much did
I spend on this
$400 ooh okay the one thing I will say
so actually as I was bringing it up I
realized that the pellets fell out so I
don't know where the pellets went
however look at this it's got a nice
little sound system and then I'm not
sure if you could see this but when I do
shoot it definitely does something this
thing is kind of annoying though
take flight it's like a sad little bird
that just won't fly what if I remove
this
fly this is so pathetic I spent good
money on
this junk absolute junk I was looking
forward to this I thought this was going
to be a lot of fun the promise of this
doing so many insane things and then
this ultimately just being this little
piece of just robot junk that can't even
take flight here we go you ready for
this fly nothing it doesn't even move
the wings the wings are broke and it
came like this have I break you cuz you
just broke my
wallet I'm not going to do that I'm not
a destructive person moving on the next
item we're taking a look at is the
singing and dancing Cactus you may have
seen videos of this before but it's a
baby's toy so I don't know why I was
drawn to it not sure what that says
about me but basically what it does is
it sings and it dances so you could tell
it to say something and apparently it
says it back to you it'll also dance to
a nice tune so it's a really nice fun
enjoyable toy if you need to be
stimulated which I guess we're about to
be so let's try this all right he's
about to come to
life okay he's on he's alive okay he's
on he's alive repeat everything I'm
about to say to you right now hello my
name is Sam and I'm an awesome person
repeat everything I'm about to say to
you right now hello my name is Sam and
I'm an awesome person wo wo okay you
don't have to copy me every like only
copy me when I say copy okay okay you
copy me when I say copy okay so there's
also some other buttons like music so
let's check this out happyday to you
happy birthday to you okay repeat after
me okay repeat you look like a poppy
playtime villain and I can see you being
a lot of fun with kids so I actually
want to give you your props here you
look like a poy playtime I wasn't I
wasn't finished I wasn't finished I
wasn't finished I wasn't finished wasn't
finished I wasn't finished no no no no
you weren't talking I'm talking to you I
don't want you to talk back at me
because I am the master and you are just
this little puppet and you know that at
any given you weren't talking I'm
talking to you I don't want you to talk
back at me because I am the master and
you are just this little puppet you were
nothing you are a literal $12 toy from U
that I purchased and now you're coming
into here the audacity to come to my
house with my rules $12 toy from teu
that I purchased and now you're coming
into the audacity to come to my house
you are the biggest waste of money I've
ever spent in my entire life and that's
saying a lot because I bought this piece
of crap and this is actually better than
you because it doesn't talk to me stop
talking I'm talking I'm done with you
waste of money I can't deal with this
thing I don't know what to do with it I
don't want to break it because I'm not a
rude person I know some kid out there
would love to have this so what I'm
going to do is I'm going to box you up
and I'm going to return you the next
potential scam ad is this rechargeable
face mask which I think I found on like
Amazon for like $150 but the Teemu
version is
$14.72 it is the 14th bestselling item
in Beauty Tools so I went ahead and
purchased it so let's see if this is a
scam all right so here we have it right
here the beauty mask kind of looks like
a Phantom of the Opera mask let's open
it up and I mean it is exactly that it
is this face kind of looks scary not
going to lie it's not something I really
want to put on my face but of course I'm
going to it's rechargeable what does
that mean ooh look at this if you ever
seen like red light therapy on your face
I think this is what it's supposed to be
okay so it's USBC on the bottom all
right here we have it red light mask
what am I supposed to do now how is this
a beauty tool what is this working
there's this like flashing red light on
my face but I don't know what's
happening if I don't come out and I look
like handsome Squidward then this thing
doesn't work 3 2
1 all right I don't know why I don't
know why I bought this this was a waste
of $15 it may work over time if you do
it like every single night I'm not sure
what I expected I just want to see if
kind of worked maybe I secretly wanted
one of these so if you see me in like a
month and I have like the most beautiful
face like I look like a Korean actor
then you know this is the reason I guess
it looks cool though to have like a
mannequin mask you know so if I ever
want to do something crazy go to like a
Halloween mask party I can show up like
this but then you guys would know it's
me so it kind of defeats the purpose so
moving on I don't know if it's just me
but when I came across this item I
thought there was no shot this is real
for the amount of dollars that they're
asking for $3 and you can get this Tik
Tock scroll YouTube short scroll thing
so it connects to your mobile device and
then even though shorts is so lazy that
you just sit there and scroll this lets
you even P your phone down you hold the
device and you can just rot in the
corner and just scroll so if you're on
my page and you want to just watch a
bunch of shorts like right here you
could just do this and it would work I
don't believe that so I'm a little bit
skeptical let's see if it works this is
it right here it's very tiny now the big
things I'm looking for here is comfort
and it actually working and I think one
of those is going to fail us look how
big this is it fits on my thumb that's
how tiny it is you can't even see the
buttons are so small okay it's on I'm
pairing it with my device now apparently
I'm connected there only one way to find
out so I'm going on shorts oh look it's
me oh so I could adjust the volume
that's it it's only letting me adjust
the volume maybe it really is Tik Tok
specific okay I have a Taco Bell
ad no it only lets me adjust the down
volume scam alert it's only $3 though so
I'm not really too mad about that but $3
I mean that's what 20 minutes work for
minimum wage worker which is decent time
so regardless of who you are you
probably should not be wasting $34
especially on this because take it from
me I tried it I bought it it does not
work it only works the volume down this
thing is a scam I'm going to go ahead
and throw this behind me right now
explosion all right guys so that's it we
tested out about 10 different items on
teu that could have sworn would have
been scams but honestly like seven or
eight of them were really good products
and I'll probably use at some point in
my life going forward so good job Teemu
I'm proud of you I did not expect that
it looks like China actually does make
products that can compete with the US so
cud is to you guys thank you guys so
much for watching though if you want to
see more content make sure to click here
click here otherwise subscribe on your
way out and I'll see you next time peace